Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Subject Files and Photographs, 1888-2004
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine subject files and photographs, 1888-2004.
24-4-3385
32.2 cubic feet.2 oversize folders.
Correspondence, Manuscripts, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection contains materials relating to the history and founding of the College, administration and various departments including academics, the clinic, and buildings.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine was founded in 1894. It was originally named the New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection contains materials relating to the history and founding of the College, administration and various departments including academics, the clinic, and buildings. Included are reports, notes, files, course materials, evaluations, handbooks, building plans, calendars, schedules, newspaper clippings, flyers, sketches, posters, photographs, rosters, sketches, directories, programs, postcards, photographs, slides, films, and guest books.
Also includes faculty biographical files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Veterinary Medicine.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Administration.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Students.; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine--Alumni and alumnae.
Subjects:
Veterinary medicine--New York (State)--Ithaca.; Veterinary medicine--Study and teaching.
Form and Genre Terms:
Building plans.; Calendars.; Directories.; Film clips.; Flyers (printed matter).; Photographs.; Picture postcards.; Posters.; Programs.; Rosters; Schedules (time plans).; Sketches.; Slides (photographs).; Visitors' books.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
See also the Veterinary College of Medicine Biomedical Communications Dept. records, #24-14-3352 and the Veterinary College of Medicine Dept. of Communications records, #24-10-3338.
SERIES LIST
Series I. History and Founding
Series II. Academic Miscellaneous
Series III. Administrative Miscellaneous
Series IV. Alumni and Students
Photographs and Slides
Series V. Buildings and Facilities
Photographs
Series VI. Calenders and Schedules
Series VII. Committees and Boards
Series VIII. Departments, Units, and Services
Photographs and Slides
Series IX. Events and classes
Photographs and Slides
Series X. Faculty and Staff
Biographical Files (including photographs)
Millennium Video Project Interviews
Faculty Portraits
Series XI. Offices and Functions
Series XII. Programs and Conferences
Series XIII. Graphics and Audiovisual Material
Series XIV. Miscellaneous
Photographs and Slides
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. History and Founding
  - Founding of the College (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Histories of the College (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copy of James Law's Last Will and Testament, 1921; Slides of Buildings and Labs from 1800s-1900s, 1800s-1921 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Legacy of Women in Veterinary Medicine - printout of website, copy of Dean Donald Smith's Keynote Address, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Series II. Academic Miscellaneous
  - General (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Scholarships (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Short Course for Veterinarians, 1901 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Senior Seminars-Guidelines, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Senior Seminars-Clinical Reports, 1961-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Senior Seminars-Clinical Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Six Years Course for Dual Degree DVM/MD, ca. 1890's (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Class Notes
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Anatomy, 1938-1939 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Blood and Urine Analysis, ca. 1938-1942 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Dairy I (pre-vet), 1938 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - Ophthalmology, ca. 1938-1942 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Leo Wuori's notes - General Surgery w/ A.G. Danks, ca. 1938-1942 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Zimmerman's Files, 1931-1935 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Exams
    - Anatomy, 1917-1947, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Animal Husbandry, 1926-1938 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bacteriology, 1897-1947, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Pathogenic Bacteriology, 1927-1937 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Chemistry, 1925-1935, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Embryology, 1926-1934 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - English, 1931-1934 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Histology, 1924-1936 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Infectious Diseases, 1929-1931, 1947, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Small Animal Diseases and Large Animal Diseases, 1927-1950 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Meat and Dairy Inspection, 1897-1923 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Dairy Industry, 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Materia Medica and Pharmacology, 1925-1937, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Medicine, 1926-1934, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Military Department, Veterinary Unit, 1927-1928 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Parasitology, 1924-1931, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - General Pathology, 1897-1924, 1938, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Special Pathology, 1910-1916 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Pathology of Infectious Diseases, 1900-1922 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Physiology, 1918-1945 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Poultry Diseases, 1931-1939 (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Infectious Diseases (W.A. Hagan), 1933 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Surgery, 1926-1947, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Veterinary Science 120 and Surgical Anatomy, 1950s (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous, ca. 1900-1915, 1927-1932, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Exams and Notes - Vertebrate Zoology, ca. 1932-1935 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Course Syllabi
    - Pathology, ca. 1896-1915 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Parasitology, ca. 1932 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Food Hygeine, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Genetic Reproduction, 1953 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous A-D, ca. 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Experimental Physiology, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Experimental Physiology, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous F-W, ca. 1955-1958 (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Clinical Pathology Conference, 1964-1970 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Information About the Collection of Syllabi from the 190s and 1970s, 1971, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Avian Diseases 255 and 557, ca.1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Pathogenic Microbiology 340, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Microbiology 515-517, 519, 705, 706, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Physiology - General, 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Physiology 526 and 527, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Pharmacology 528 and Toxicology 621, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Anatomy 500-506, 700, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Anatomy 500 - Gross Anatomy, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Anatomy 501, 503-506, 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Anatomy 507, 508, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Pathology 535-537, 571, 740, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Veterinary Pathology, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Large animal Medicine, Obstetrics and Surgery 561-566, 683, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Clinical Courses 568, 569, 571-578, ca.1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Small Animal Medicine 586-584, folder 1, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Small Animal Medicine 586-584, folder 2, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Small Animal Surgery 585-587, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Small Animal Ophthalmology 588, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Physiology 611 and 612, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Special Pathology 632, ca. 1970-1975 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Animal Parasitology 635, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Bacteriology and Immunology 641, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Food Quality Control 730, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Applied Parasitology 731, 1969-1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Veterinary Medicine 740 - Epidemiological Methods, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Diseases of Poultry, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Physical Biology 920 - Elements of Physical Biology, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Physical Biology 921, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Physical Biology 922 - Biological Effects of Radiation, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Physical Biology 923 - Biological Membranes and Nutrient Transfer, Robert Wasserman, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Physical Biology 924 - Functional Organization of the Nervous System, ca. 1967 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Other Divisions - Mostly Animal Science, ca. 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous, ca. 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - "Core Course Syllabi for the New Curriculum", Dec. 1972 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Elective Course, Folder 1, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Elective Course, Folder 2, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Core Courses 500-516, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Core Courses 517-526, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Core Courses 527-626, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Veterinary Mycology 516, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Veterinary Virology and Viral Diseases 517, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Class of 1997 Learning Objectives, 1993 (Box 14)
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: Neck, Abscesses-Tumors
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Small Animal Surgery: Head, Neck, Trunk, and Genital Organs and Extremities
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: HEAD, Fractures-Wounds
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: EXTREMITIES, Open Joint-Tendonitis
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: EXTREMITIES, Abcesses-Navicular Diseases
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: EXTREMITIES, Tendo-Vaginitis Wounds
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: Trunk and Genital Organs Fractures-Wounds
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: Trunk and Genital Organs Abscesses-Fistulous Withers
  - Clinical Notes, 1896-1918 (Box 18)
    Large Animal Surgery: HEAD, Abscesses-Floating Teeth
  - Department of Pathology and Bacteriology (Box 20)
    Clinical Notes
  - Publishing Notes for animal diseases and ailments (Box 22)
- Series III. Administrative Miscellaneous
  - American Veterinary Medical Association Evaluation Report, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - American Veterinary Medical Association Evaluation, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Budget Requests-State College Council, 1933-1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Budget Requests, 1959-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Master Plan, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Master Plan, 1973-1980 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - N.Y.S. Senate Evaluation of the College, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Self Study Report to American Veterinary Medical Association, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Series IV. Alumni and Students
  - Alumni Association (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Alumni Lists (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Graduate Students (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Organizations
    - Alpha Psi (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Omega Tau Sigma (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Phi Zeta (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Society of Comparative Medicine, 1904-1908 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Society of Comparative Medicine, 1909-1916 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - General, 1939-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - General, 1963-1965, 1978-1981, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Minutes, 1947-1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Newsletters (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Directories (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - SCAVMA/JAVMA - Dues and Attendance Records, ca. 1960s (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Student Handbooks, 1952-1980 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Student Handbooks, 1993,1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - "Measures" Unofficial News Bulletin of the Students of the NYS VC, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous Organizations (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Graduate Students - Lists, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Class files, 1897-1933 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Class files, 1934 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Class files, 1935-1939 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Class files, 1940-1941 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Class files, 1942 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    Contains V-9018
  - Class files, 1943-1949 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Class files, 1950-1959 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Class files (Box 38, Folder 8)
    Contains some negatives
  - Class files, 1970-1975 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Class files, 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Class files, 1980-1985 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Class files, 1986-1989 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Class files, 1990-1996 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Class files, 2000-2005 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Photographs and Slides
  - Accreditation Site Visit, 1995 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Alumni Association, 1960s (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Alumni Association Dinner and Luncheon, 1990 and 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Students in Company C, 1943 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Graduates - slides, 1995-1997 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Students, 1990s-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Students in Clinics and Labs, 1980s-1990s (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Students in Classrooms - slides, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Students (slides), 1998-2000 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Tutorial Sessions, 2002 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Omega Tau Sigma composites and class photographs, 1920-1984 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Alpha Psi composites and class photographs, 1923-1931, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Gamma Alpha composites and class photographs, with class information, 1916-1923 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Class composites, 1900-2013 (Box 44)
  - Plaque with names of students receiving the Borden Scholarship Awards in Veterinary Medicine 1945-1953, Undated (Box 47, Folder 42)
    Item number: 900
  - Seven students in field: H Beebe, RJ Foster, B English, FD Hoford, J Knapp, JW Rosenthal, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    Item number: 101.1902.1
  - Twelve students in anatomy laboratory dissecting horses; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins is 2nd from right with black beard, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    Item number: 101.1902.2
  - Eleven students with Dr. Walter L Williams (3rd from right in derby hat) in large animal surgery, 1902 (Box 47, Folder 43)
    Item number: 101.1902.3
  - Three students under a large animal skeleton: Walter Treman, Frank Baker, John McNamara, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    Item number: 101.1904.05.1
  - Four students in front of outside door: Frank Baker, ?, John McNamara, Walter Treman, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    Item number: 101.1905.05.2
  - Large group of students in two rows in anatomy lab with upright leg of horse on left; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins seated in front (4th from left), 1904 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    Item number: 100.1904
  - Large group of students in four rows in anatomy lab; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins (center withmustashe and one left hand on lap), woman in checked overdress to right of Hopkins; black students on far right., 1904 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    Item number: 7-190-93
  - Large group of students in classes 1904 to 1906 in rows outside under the front portico of James Law Hall; with Professors James Law, Grant Sherman Hopkins, Simon Henry Gage, Walter L Williams, 1904 (Box 47, Folder 44)
    Item number: 100.1904-06
  - Large group of students in three rows in anatomy lab; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins seated (center 5th from left), 1905 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    Item number: 100.1905
  - Students in classes of 1905 and 1906 in field with a horse and attendant on bank behind, 1905 (Box 47, Folder 45)
    Item number: 101.1905-06
  - Students in class of 1906 in anatomy lab; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins (center fifth from left); students with C on jersey at far right, 1906 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    Item number: 100.1906
  - Students in class of 1907 in 3 rows in whites; professors in front row in dark suits in anatomy lab; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins (center 5th from right), 1907 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Item number: 100.1907
  - Students in class of 1907? In 3 rows in dark suits outside in front of door and ivy covered building, 1907 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    Item number: 10154
  - Students in classes 1908 to 1910 in rows outside in front of Law Hall, Expression (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Students in class of 1909 in rows, students in whites, faculty in dark suits; Professor Grant Sherman Hopkins is in 2nd row center with mustashe, 1909 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Students in class of 1910 with a horse painted with "1910"; Florence Kimball first woman graduate is seated, 1910 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    Item number: 101.191
  - Four students in class of 1912 with horse and dog, 1912 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Two rows of class of 1920 alumni taken in front of Schurman Hall, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    Item number: 101.192
  - Group of class of 1920 alumni with headquarters sign, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - 1920 class composite, 1920 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Students in class of 1923 in rows in cap-and-gown outside; faculty in center of middle row with white hoods, 1923 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    Item number: 100.1923
  - 50th Reunion of class of 1938 in 1988, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Group from class of 1939 at 55th Reunion, 1994, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - 4 Class of 1939 alumni holding a Chinese scene at 60th anniversary of class of 1939 sumitted by Dr Francis J Kwong: seated l to r: Dr Isidor Sprecher, Dr Coln "Joe"Lasher, Dr. Morris Erdheim, Dr. John Murray, 1939 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - 20th Reunion of class of 1940 in 1960; 3 row alumni, spouses and faculty, 1940 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    Item number: 60-1-7-10
  - Eight students in class of 1941 in anatomy lab with cow carcass, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Joe Feno in cap-and-gown, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Roger R Fales (for Falls?) and Dr Eric W Simmons, 1941 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Dr. Leo Wuori (left) and Dr. Roger R Fales(right) in door of building, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Students in class of 1942 in Medical Building amphitheater examining a Jersey cow, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Item number: 14265
  - Students in class of 1942 in 3 rows outside in front of the Medical Building, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    Item number: 100.1942
  - Negative of 1942 class composite, 1942 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Students in class of February 1943 in 3 rows inside with large windows behind, 1943-02 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    Item number: 100.1943-Feb
  - Students in class of October 1943 in 3 rows outside in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1943-11 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    Item number: 100.1943-Oct
  - Nine students in military uniform with Dr. Myron Fincher (center) in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Students in class of 1944 in 3 rows in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Item number: 100.1944
  - Seven students in class of 1944 in military uniform, 1944 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Item number: UP-201
  - Students in class of 1945 in 3 rows inside, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    Item number: 100.1945
  - Reunion group photo of class of 1945, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Students in class of 1946 in 3 rows outside Veterinray Medical Clinic Building, 1946 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    Item number: 100.1946
  - Students in class of 1947 in 3 rows outside Medical Clinic Building, 1947 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    Item number: RMC4-3-2882
  - Students in class of 1949 in 3 rows in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1949 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    Item number: UP4598-B
  - Students in class of 1950 in 3 rows in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    Item number: UP5516-B
  - Students in class of 1950 with spouses and children in rows on steps of Bailey Hall, 1950 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    Item number: UP5525-B
  - Student in class of 1951 in 3 rows in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Class of 1951 reunion, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Negative of 1951 class composite, 1951 (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Negative of 1952 class composite, 1952 (Box 48, Folder 23)
  - Students in class of 1953 in 4 rows in front of Medical Clinic Building, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Negative of 1953 class composite, 1953 (Box 48, Folder 24)
  - Students in class of 1955 in 4 rows outside Medical Clinic Building, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 25)
    Item number: UP7471
  - Students in class of 1955 trip to tour Lederle Lab in front of Virus Research Building, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Negative of 1955 class composite, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Negative of 1956 class composite, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Students in class of 1957 in 5 rows outside beside Barton Hall, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 27)
    Item number: 8322-2
  - Negative of 1957 class composite, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Class of 1959, 1959 (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Students outside looking at a white pitbull terrier dog, 1963 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Individual portraits of class of 1967 students, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 30)
  - Individual portraits of class of 1968 students, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 31)
  - Students in class of 1974 in 4 rows, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    Item number: 1974A
  - Students in class of 1974 in 3 rows, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 32)
    Item number: 1074B
  - Negative of 1985 class composite, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 33)
  - Negatives of 1992 class composite, 1992 (Box 48, Folder 34)
  - Negatives of 1993 class composite, 1993 (Box 48, Folder 35)
  - Rows of students and faculty under James Law Hall portico; James Law and other faculty in front row seated, 1922?, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Item number: 01-385
  - Rows of students in light colored suits with faculty seated in front of Medical Clinic Building, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Two rows of students in office with Prof. Donald W Baker in center standing, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Item number: 521
  - Twelve students in 2 rows outside brick wall of James Law Hall, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - 4 rows of students in dark suits in front of a curtain; Dr. Hadley Stephenson (2nd row 2nd from left); Dr. Myron Fincher (4th row 5th fron left), Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Misc photos of students in parade, at party, with parade models, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - 6 alumni standing in front of a table with petri dishes: HC Parker '27, FI Reed '26, SD Johnson '29, WG Hoag '44, KI Gumaer '43. EW Tucker '41, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - 3 alumni at signature of a book: R Gilyard '35, F Bushnell '33, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Item number: UP-3423-D
  - 3 alumni seated signing a book: SF Sheidy Upenn '29, WC Glenney ISU '36, 1948 (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Item number: UP-3423-G
  - 2 alumni at banquet: Dr John D Wheat, Dr Andy Morse, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Item number: 11368
  - 2 rows of students of 13 students; student in flowered dress seated in center, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
    Item number: 105
  - 3 rows of students and faculty; student in flowered dress seated at right, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Group at Commencement: (l to r) Dr. Alexander deLahunta, Dean Donald F Smith, President Lehman's wife Kathy Okun, Dr. Bruce Widger, Mrs Donald F "Doris" Smith, Dr. Jerry Belinski, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Group photo taken at Tavern on the Green, New York City, July 31 2006 with Dean Donald Smith, Dr Harold Zweighaft and others, Undated (Box 48, Folder 36)
  - Cooper Curtice, Undated (Box 48, Folder 37)
    Item number: 600.c978
  - Numerous b/w photos of individual and small groups of students taken by University Photography between 1974 and 1984, 1974-1984 (Box 48, Folder 41)
  - Daniel Elmer Salmon - charcoal etching - without frame, Undated (Box 48, Folder 38)
    Item number: 11-437-85
  - Daniel Elmer Salmon - charcoal etching - with frame and matte, Undated (Box 48, Folder 38)
    Item number: 11-436-85
  - Theobald Smith, Undated (Box 48, Folder 39)
    Item number: 3-180-86